It's time for us to go thicky thicky for the record with comedian Shantae Wayans.
Y'all know how it goes. I give them the scenario, they give me the song.
We're going to learn about Shantae through the music that she loves.
Well, that last name that you have is one that we all know fairly well.
What is a song that reminds you of your family?
I would say the Jackson Fire because I think that it just represents us as a whole.
Just all of us being on stage, all of us having some type of talent and in the form of bonding with our family because we're pretty tight.
Was there ever any time where you were like, I don't want to be a comic.
I don't want to be like you guys. I'm going to be an insect.
An insect?
I'm going to be an insect scientist.
Like, was there ever any like...
Insect scientist.
No, I actually never wanted to be in the industry.
I'm heavy into tech. I still am.
I learned very well from that, but I wanted to be computer science.
And when I picked three colleges to go to and only got...
I got accepted to two.
I wound up going to Seton Hall and I wish I would have went to Hampton.
And because I didn't, I felt very like sane.
It was boring. I felt like it was an extension of high school.
And so I stopped doing that and I moved out here.
Got on production and that like changed everything for me.
We are...